

PROFILE

Seasoned and independent Front End Developer with 5+ years of experience in blending the art of design with the skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging. Very passionate about Emerging Tech and UI / UX design.

EXPERIENCE

•	Dec 2021 - Dec 2022	Software Developer OpenEyes Technologies Inc.
•	Sep 2020 - Nov 2021	Software Engineer Future Link Consultants
•	Jan 2020 - Jul 2020	Jr. Software Engineer CodeZeros
•	Jun 2017 -	Web Designer

PORTFOLIO

Padmavati Online Services

Dec 2019

https://neelams-portfolio.netlify.app/ https://neelam-r.webflow.io/

NEELAM Chawla



React Developer

+91 - 787 44 88 555

neelam.projects@gmail.com

(in) www.linkedin.com/in/neelam-r/

Vadodara, Gujarat

EDUCATION

 Post Graduate Diploma in Network Administration

2017 - Gujarat University

Master of Computer Applications
 2015 - Sikkim Manipal University

Bachelor of Computer Applications
 2013 - Sikkim Manipal University

SKILLSET

React / Angular / Vue
JavaScript / ES6 / JSX / TypeScript
MySql / PostgreSQL / MongoDB
HTML / PHP - Laravel
CSS / SASS / Figma / Adobe - (XD, PS)
Tailwind CSS / Bootstrap
Kendo UI / Material UI / Semantic UI
Firebase / GitHub / Netlify / Heroku / Gatsby
WordPress / Shopify
(Basic Knowledge of Grunt)

FRAMEWORKS



